<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HackOverflow</string>
    <string name="title_about">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_notice">Notification</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Signed In</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string-array name="colorArray">
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Cyan</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Black</item>
        <item>Gray</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Purple</item>
        <item>Pink</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Brown</item>
        <item>Gold</item>
        <item>Silver</item>
        <item>Violet</item>
        <item>Indigo</item>
        <item>Magenta</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="livingBeingArray">
        <item>Fox</item>
        <item>Whale</item>
        <item>Spider</item>
        <item>Bear</item>
        <item>Wolf</item>
        <item>Lion</item>
        <item>Tiger</item>
        <item>Elephant</item>
        <item>Giraffe</item>
        <item>Hippo</item>
        <item>Raccoon</item>
        <item>Squirrel</item>
        <item>Penguin</item>
        <item>Gorilla</item>
        <item>Jaguar</item>
        <item>Kangaroo</item>
        <item>Otter</item>
        <item>Puma</item>
        <item>Quail</item>
        <item>Hedgehog</item>
        <item>Dragon</item>
        <item>Leopard</item>
        <item>Owl</item>
        <item>Pelican</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="noNoticeArray">
        <item>Hackathon mode: activated. Notifications: deactivated.</item>
        <item>We\'re in the zone, no notifications allowed!</item>
        <item>Hacking away, notifications can wait.</item>
        <item>No notifications, just code and caffeine.</item>
        <item>We\'re hacking like it\'s 1999, notifications be gone!</item>
        <item>Sorry notifications, this is a hackathon, you\'re not invited!</item>
        <item>Our focus is on hacking, not on notifications.</item>
        <item>Notifications? We\'ve got bigger fish to fry.</item>
        <item>Notifications? We\'ve got hacking to do.</item>
        <item>Quiet as a library, not a single notification in sight.</item>
        <item>All clear, no notifications to see here.</item>
        <item>A moment of peace, no notifications to disturb.</item>
        <item>A notification-free zone, enjoy the tranquility.</item>
        <item>You\'re the chosen one! Find Rishabh to break out of the Matrix.     - Morpheus</item>
        <item>No buzzing, no beeping, just silence.</item>
        <item>Currently experiencing a notification drought.</item>
        <item>The calm before the notification storm.</item>
        <item>Notifications? None. Relax and enjoy the silence.</item>
        <item>No alerts, no interruptions, just you and your hackathon.</item>
        <item>Notifications at bay, focus on coding and creating.</item>
        <item>Nothing to see here, move along.</item>
        <item>All quiet on the notification front.</item>
        <item>The silence is deafening.</item>
        <item>No updates, no news, just peace and quiet.</item>
        <item>Notifications? None to be found.</item>
        <item>No alerts, no fuss, just chill.</item>
        <item>Not a peep from the notification world.</item>
        <item>No updates to report, carry on with your day.</item>
        <item>Notifications? Not in our hackathon vocabulary.</item>
        <item>The hackathon is in session, notifications are adjourned.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="collegeUnderConstruction">
        <item>The college secrets are so top-notch, we need a little extra time to gather all the information. Hang tight, it\'s worth the wait!</item>
        <item>We\'re putting the finishing touches on the college details section. It\'s going to be a masterpiece, trust us!</item>
        <item>The About College section is currently undergoing renovations. Think of it as a spa day for your brain, we\'re making it even better!</item>
        <item>Our team of detective elves are hard at work gathering all the details about the college. They\'ll have everything ready soon, we promise!</item>
        <item>The About College section is taking a little break to catch its breath, but it\'ll be back soon with all the details you need to know. Just like your favorite TV show, it\'ll be worth the wait!</item>
        <item>The About College section is in the oven, cooking up some juicy details for you. Stay tuned for the feast!</item>
        <item>We know you\'re eager to learn more about our college, but patience is a virtue. Our About College section is just around the corner.</item>
        <item>Construction in progress! But we promise, this section will be a work of art when we\'re done.</item>
        <item>We\'re working hard to bring you the best and most comprehensive information about our college. Hang in there!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="creditsUnderConstruction">
        <item>The credits page is coming soon! Just like a great movie, the people behind the scenes are just as important.</item>
        <item>We\'re putting together a list of all the hardworking individuals and technologies that made this hackathon &amp; app possible. Hang tight, it\'s on its way!</item>
        <item>Stay tuned, we\'re gathering all the details of the team and technologies that helped make this app a reality. It\'s going to be a page worth reading!</item>
        <item>The credits page is taking a quick nap, but it\'ll be back with all the names and contributions of the real MVPs. Stay tuned, it\'s going to be legendary!</item>
        <item>Our credits page is like a time capsule, preserving the memories of the heroes behind this hackathon. We just need a little more time to finish it.</item>
        <item>The credits page is undergoing some polishing, adding the shining names of the people who made this hackathon possible. It\'ll be ready soon, we promise!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="aboutCollege">Pillai HOC College of Engineering and Technology is a leading institution in technology education, offering a state-of-the-art learning environment with modern facilities and experienced faculty. The college is hosting a hackathon in March 2023 and seeking sponsorship from technology companies to provide opportunities for students to showcase their skills and connect with industry leaders. The Department of Computer Engineering at Pillai HOC College of Engineering and Technology emphasizes both technical and ethical education, promoting innovative problem-solving and environmental protection. The department regularly organizes events such as Tech Thrive and Code Fest and encourages students to participate in hackathons, having achieved AIR 1 in the Smart India Hackathon 2022. The college invites companies in the technology industry to join in their efforts to enhance student learning experiences through the upcoming hackathon. </string>


    <string name="hof_about_1">HackOverflow is a 3-day National level hackathon organized by the Department of Computer Engineering at Pillai\'s HOC College of Engineering and Technology.</string>
    <string name="hof_about_2">This Hackathon will be conducted from 16th-18th March in two separate (Offline &amp; Online) modes with separate winners and prizes/swags.</string>
    <string name="hof_about_3">The offline mode will take place on the 14-acre PHCET campus, providing participants with Food, Accommodation, Placement Opportunity, and Goodies for all participants.</string>
    <string name="hof_about_4">Get all details related to HackOverflow and both modes (Offline &amp; Online) in our Hackathon\'s Brochure.</string>

    <string name="college_about_1">Pillai HOC College of Engineering and Technology is a leading institution in technology education that offers a state-of-the-art learning environment with modern facilities and experienced faculty.</string>
    <string name="college_about_2">PHCET is inviting student developers from around the country to participate in a hackathon in March 2023, providing opportunities to showcase their skills and connect with industry leaders.</string>
    <string name="college_about_3">The Department of Computer Engineering at PHCET emphasizes both technical and ethical education, promoting innovative problem-solving and environmental protection.</string>
    <string name="college_about_4">The department regularly organizes events such as Tech Thrive and Code Fest and encourages students to participate in hackathons, having 2 teams that achieved AIR 1 in the Smart India Hackathon 2022.</string>

    <string name="credits_about_1">We\'re truly in awe of the super-powered team behind this hackathon! Their relentless efforts and mad skills have brought this event to life.</string>
    <string name="credits_about_2">A big shoutout to the whole organizing team, open-source libraries and APIs who lent a helping hand in creating this app. They are the real MVPs!</string>
    <string name="credits_about_3">Discover all the credits to the individuals, APIs, and key libraries that made this hackathon and this app happen, below.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="college_about_5">Click below to view more details and pictures of the college and computer engineer department.</string>
    <string name="update_text">An update\'s headed your way! Buckle up, things are about to get even better!\n\nUpdate the app from the Google Play Store by clicking below.</string>
    <string name="title_feed">Feed</string>
    <string name="textFeed">Post on Twitter/LinkedIn with #PHCET &amp; #HackOverflow to get your posts featured here, and every few random posters will win swags &amp; goodies. ;)</string>

</resources>